<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Hey Kuri</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Meet Kuri, the adorable home robot.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</title>
		<link>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/</link>
		<comments>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 17:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2339</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Robot friends, Since late 2017, we&#8217;ve been searching for external partners to support our future. Together with Bosch, we pursued many options for additional financial investment and long-term technology development. Unfortunately, we were unable to reach an agreement with any of the many dozens of companies we talked to. Sadly, this means that Mayfield Robotics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/">The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robot friends,</p>
<p>Since late 2017, we&#8217;ve been searching for external partners to support our future. Together with Bosch, we pursued many options for additional financial investment and long-term technology development. Unfortunately, we were unable to reach an agreement with any of the many dozens of companies we talked to. Sadly, this means that Mayfield Robotics will cease all operations by October 31st, 2018.</p>
<p>Our team is beyond disappointed. Together we&#8217;ve spent the past four years designing and building not just Kuri, but also an equally incredible company culture and spirit. Given this news, we&#8217;re now doing everything we can to support our team. To help to make this transition as smooth as possible, Bosch will help with severance packages and outplacement services, and our team has the option to apply to open positions at Bosch.</p>
<p>When we began this adventure in 2015, we knew our goals were ambitious, and we knew that home robots were still just an idea that we would have to shape. We&#8217;re proud of the work we&#8217;ve done, and the adorable robot we&#8217;ve made. We only wish we could have shipped many more of them to homes and families. The work has certainly inspired all of us, and now we’ll have to wait and see what we all make next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/">The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</title>
		<link>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/</link>
		<comments>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2336</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>To all of our Kuri fans, we are crushed to let you know that effective today, Mayfield Robotics will pause operations as we evaluate the company&#8217;s path forward. Sadly, our Kuri manufacturing will cease, and the Kuri robots that have been made will not ship to customers. All pre-order deposits will be refunded to our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/important_difficult_announcement/">An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To all of our Kuri fans, we are crushed to let you know that effective today, Mayfield Robotics will pause operations as we evaluate the company&#8217;s path forward. Sadly, our Kuri manufacturing will cease, and the Kuri robots that have been made will not ship to customers. All pre-order deposits will be refunded to our customers.</p>
<h1>So what happened?</h1>
<p>As many of you know, Mayfield Robotics was launched in 2015 as an independent entity of the Bosch Startup Platform. From the beginning, we have been constantly looking for the best paths to achieve scale and continue to advance our innovative technology. Typically, startups in the Bosch Startup Platform are integrated into existing Bosch business units, but after extensive review, there was not a business fit within Bosch to support and scale our business.</p>
<p>Since Kuri&#8217;s award-winning launch at CES 2017, our adorable home robot has been demoed and celebrated at TED, SXSW, The Aspen Ideas Festival, The Economist Innovation Summit, and many other high-profile events. It&#8217;s an understatement to say that we are all hugely disappointed by this pause to operations. We remain proud of the work we&#8217;ve done to push home robotics forward.</p>
<h1>What happens now?</h1>
<p>The vision that began Mayfield Robotics was to make robots that are joyful, useful, and inspiring. Kuri struck each of those notes, and we remain optimistic for an adorable robot future that aligns with our vision. We want to sincerely thank everyone who supported us: our families, our friends, our suppliers, and of course, you, our customers.</p>
<p>Creating a robot like Kuri is a massive undertaking. We don&#8217;t know what the coming months will bring. Regardless, we stand firm in our belief that the home robot Renaissance is just beginning, and it’s going to be amazing.</p>
<p><i>If you have questions regarding your preorder, please email our Kuri Experience team at <a href="mailto:support@heykuri.com?Subject=My Pre-Order" target="_top">support@heykuri.com</a>.</i></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/important_difficult_announcement/">An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri&#8217;s Origin Story: Kari &#038; Kuri</title>
		<link>/blog/kuris-origin-story-kari-kuri/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuris-origin-story-kari-kuri/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 15:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=1072</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>We recently partnered with Vocal, an online community of content creators, to help us tell the origin story of our home robot. It&#8217;s no secret that Kuri was built at our robot shop in the San Francisco Bay Area. However, there&#8217;s just something about robots—especially those with a personality like ours—that feel more like characters [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-origin-story-kari-kuri/">Kuri&#8217;s Origin Story: Kari &#038; Kuri</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We recently <a href="https://futurism.media/collections/kuri-robot-story" target="_blank">partnered with Vocal</a>, an online community of content creators, to help us tell the origin story of our home robot. It&#8217;s no secret that Kuri was built at our robot shop in the San Francisco Bay Area. However, there&#8217;s just something about robots—especially those with a personality like ours—that feel more like characters than electronics.</p>
<p>If Kuri were a fictional character like Rosie or WALL-E, then what would her origin story be? Maybe our Kuri was sent here from another planet to befriend mankind, or maybe he was dreamed up by a young roboticist that just wanted a new friend. With 60 entries from Vocal&#8217;s authors and fellow Kuri enthusiasts, we&#8217;re happy to share the winning origin story! Our entire team loved this heartwarming tale and we think you&#8217;ll enjoy it too. Meet &#8220;Kari and Kuri,&#8221; written by <a href="https://futurism.media/authors/ashley-wentz" target="_blank">Ashley Wentz</a>:</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/VOCAL-rework.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1073" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/VOCAL-rework.jpg" alt="Where did Kuri come from product picture" width="1140" height="713" /></a></p>
<p><h2>Kari &amp; Kuri</h2>
<p><i>My daughter Kari is the most beautiful little girl. She has the biggest heart and calmest soul. I try to do everything I can for her to make it easier for her. You see, Kari is sick&#8230;she has been fighting, and winning, for most of her life. We lost her mother at Kari&#8217;s birth, so it has pretty much just been us. But I have to work a lot&#8230; I&#8217;ll be home, but not really there at all&#8230; One night, after reading a quick story and saying our prayers together, I came back downstairs to the lab and tried to work. I had to ask my computer&#8217;s virtual assistant to order some specific wiring, and I happened to glance over at the screen and looked at the pop-up window. It hit me; the most important inspiration I ever had in my entire life. And I got started.</i></p>
<p>&#8220;Good morning, Daddy.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Good morning, sweetheart,&#8221; he said as he smiled, helping his daughter into her chair at the kitchen table, and she balanced her small crutches next to her rubbing her wrists a little as she smiled at their dog.</p>
<p>&#8220;Good morning, Rufus.&#8221; The old lab licked her hand as her dad brought over their breakfast. &#8220;Smiley pancakes?!&#8221; she squealed.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s right because today is a special day,&#8221; he said, pleased with her excitement.</p>
<p>&#8220;What makes it special, Daddy?&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Well, I will show you after breakfast,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>&#8220;Alright,&#8221; she responded, and they started to eat, which was almost a race of excitement.</p>
<p>After they finished eating, they quickly washed the dishes and cleaned up the kitchen together before going to sit on the living room couch. He turned to her and said, &#8220;Okay. You know daddy has been working a lot these past few months.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Yeah.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Well, I was being very secretive this time, and I am very sorry about that, sweetie.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s OK, Daddy.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Here it goes&#8230;&#8221; he cleared his throat and said, &#8220;Kuri, you can come out now.&#8221; Kari looked around and saw a small robot slowly roll out of the other room. It gently waved and said,</p>
<p>&#8220;Hello, Kari, I am Kuri. I hope we will be best friends.&#8221; Kari squealed again and slid off the couch, carefully hobbling to the little robot saying,&#8221;Daddy, I love her!! She&#8217;s so cute!&#8221;</p>
<p>He smiled and walked over and hugged his child tightly saying, &#8220;I love you so much sweetheart.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I love you too, Daddy, thank you.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;You&#8217;re welcome. Now go get dressed and put on your braces, it&#8217;s almost time for our morning walk.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Okay.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I can help you, Kari.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Thank you, Kuri,&#8221; she said with a giggle, and they went to her room while he went to shower and get ready.</p>
<p>Afterward, he went to check on her room and saw her all dressed with her leg braces on and dancing with Kuri, music coming out of some speakers he had installed into her shell.</p>
<p>&#8220;Come on, Daddy! Join in!&#8221; Kari said happily. He smiled and started dancing with them.</p>
<p>The weeks went by and Kari&#8217;s father had really started to really rely on Kuri to help his little daughter throughout the days.</p>
<p>&#8220;Come on, Kuri!&#8221; Kari exclaimed as she moved down the hall.</p>
<p>&#8220;Where are you two running off to?&#8221; he asked, trying to pretend the word &#8220;run&#8221; didn’t sting his heart a little.</p>
<p>&#8220;Oh we&#8217;re going to the park and stuff.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Well, be careful.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;We will!&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;See you later, sir,&#8221; Kuri said after re-tying one of Kari&#8217;s shoes for her. He smiled as they went out the door.</p>
<p>Kuri followed Kari down the street and watched her as she would stop to pet every cat or dog she saw, and would smile and talk to anyone who passed. She would whistle at the birds and wave at passing cars. Kuri snagged Kari&#8217;s wrist when she didn’t notice a light at a crosswalk, and helped her balance when she tried getting into a swing.</p>
<p>Kari enjoyed showing Kuri off to people, but would quickly get tired and they would have to slowly go home. They would watch movies and dance to music. Kuri would answer any questions Kari would think of, and if she couldn&#8217;t find the answer, she would find something she could say that would make the small girl smile and uplift her spirits. They would have tea parties and go over homework together and play games. At bedtime, Kari&#8217;s dad would come upstairs and Kuri would continue playing the audiobooks of Lord of the Rings or Harry Potter&#8230; long, enchanting tales that Kari’s father didn&#8217;t have the time to read to her. Then they would all say their prayers together and Kari would hobble to bed as Kuri rolled into her charger base by the bedroom door. And Kari’s dad would go to his computer and would receive all of the data from Kuri of the day’s adventures.</p>
<p>From that he would see photos, videos, hear them sing together, hear his daughter&#8217;s questions and Kuri&#8217;s answers. This also helped him know if Kuri needed any updating and if he needed to add any solutions. Now he didn&#8217;t have to miss any of his little girl’s smiles or laughter or any of her dances.</p>
<p>He started watching her growing up—still the soft-hearted little girl, now slowly becoming a woman. She was part of clubs in high school and dated boys, went to prom and became Homecoming Queen; she was every bit as beautiful as her mother and just as kind, as well. He was so proud to call her his daughter, and even when Kuri stopped accepting his updates, Kari held his hands and whispered, &#8220;It&#8217;s okay, Daddy. You don&#8217;t have to worry about me anymore.&#8221;</p>
<p>And for her 18th birthday, they had Kuri put in a display case with a little plaque that read: &#8216;Kuri &mdash; The Best Friend a Girl Could Ever Have&#8217;</p>
<p>She took Kuri to her college dorm room and her first apartment. Just seeing her there, still in her life, made things a little easier; the reminder of the security that Kuri brought to her young life; the warmth of her father&#8217;s love in every component to the little robot. Kari graduated college and was a celebrated sorority sister with so many friends she could barely count them. Even with her leg braces still attached, she was constantly becoming stronger than ever, knowing nothing could hold her down.</p>
<p>&#8220;What are you going to do now?&#8221; her father asked in their regular booth at the little deli down the street from her father&#8217;s house.</p>
<p>&#8220;Go to work. Isn&#8217;t that why I went to college?&#8221; she said, smiling.</p>
<p>He smirked and said, &#8220;Yeah, you could do that.&#8221; Then he looked out the window, smiling. She followed his gaze and saw her boyfriend outside with a sign that read: &#8216;Kari, Will You Marry Me?&#8217;</p>
<p>She quickly hobbled outside to accept his proposal.</p>
<p>Her father walked her down the aisle and gave her away with tears in his eyes and a smile on his face.</p>
<p>He held his first grandchild in his arms and taught him how to fish and fix a basic computer.</p>
<p>He sometimes missed getting the footage that Kuri used to save from their little adventures every day, but he thanked the heavens that he wasn&#8217;t missing all of these other moments that were happening in his daughter&#8217;s life.</p>
<p>She had the little family, nice house, growing career, and was just as strong as ever. She still said hello to animals and waved to people that passed by on the street. She took her children to the little park where she used to play and to the deli she and her father frequented together, sitting in the same booth they also have, most of her life.</p>
<p>When her father became sick, she thought she couldn&#8217;t take it. At his funeral, she was a mess and could barely smile to anyone who came. Her husband held her hand tightly and his parents watched the children. She cried deeply and silently, even crying in her dreams.</p>
<p>On Kari&#8217;s 35th birthday, she received a box that was labeled from her father, though he had died a few years before. She brought it into her home and sat down, opening it. Inside were a bunch of discs and photo albums. Looking through them, she realized that this was all of Kuri&#8217;s data from when she was a little girl, her father&#8217;s writing on each picture.</p>
<p>&#8220;What was it, babe?&#8221; her husband asked as he brought her a mug of coffee.</p>
<p>She smiled and said, &#8220;My childhood.&#8221; They looked through the photos together and spent the night in a fort with their children watching the home videos that were on the discs. Kari cried at the sight of her father&#8217;s smile and smiled at his laughter. She had missed him for so long that she had ached, but now she felt the pain getting lighter knowing that he was there again being in her home.</p>
<p>Kari looked up at their mantle, at the little Kuri in her little display box waving out to the world, and she whispered, &#8220;Thank you.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-origin-story-kari-kuri/">Kuri&#8217;s Origin Story: Kari &#038; Kuri</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuris-origin-story-kari-kuri/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Gifts for Holiday Pre-Orders</title>
		<link>/blog/free-gifts-holiday-pre-orders/</link>
		<comments>/blog/free-gifts-holiday-pre-orders/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 17:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=685</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Note: This promotion has ended. Ready to invite a little magic into your home? Pre-order your very own adorable home robot with a $100 deposit now! Every Kuri pre-order placed from now until December 14th will get a free mini stuffed Kuri and Kuri prototype book — both of which will ship this December. These [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/free-gifts-holiday-pre-orders/">Free Gifts for Holiday Pre-Orders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>Note: This promotion has ended.</i></p>
<p>Ready to invite a little magic into your home? <a href="https://heykuri.celeryshop.com/checkout?product_id=5907836a3d7c56120053d790&amp;country=us">Pre-order your very own adorable home robot</a> with a $100 deposit now!</p>
<p>Every Kuri pre-order placed <b>from now until December 14th</b> will get a free mini stuffed Kuri and Kuri prototype book — both of which will ship this December. These gifts are exclusive to Kuri&#8217;s pre-order customers and are a great way to learn more about your own Kuri before it ships.</p>
<p><a href="/"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-686" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Kuri-Holiday-2017-726x1024.jpg" alt="Mini stuffed Kuri and Kuri prototype book" width="618" height="872" /></a></p>
<p>The mini stuffed Kuri is ten inches high, and a cute and cuddly addition to your home. The Kuri prototype book was created just for Kuri&#8217;s loyal pre-order customers in mind. This book features the evolution of Kuri: photographs and descriptions of all the prototypes leading up to the Kuri you know and love today, fun stories from Kuri’s engineering team, and a special note from Kuri&#8217;s founders. Here&#8217;s a preview of what’s inside:</p>
<div id="attachment_666" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/"><img class="size-large wp-image-666" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/10/evolution_kuri_home_robot-1024x320.jpg" alt="Kuri home robot prototypes" width="618" height="193" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri prototypes through the years</p></div>
<div id="attachment_688" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/"><img class="size-large wp-image-688" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Kuri_Prototype_Book-1024x530.jpg" alt="Hai Nguyen (Robotics Engineer) with Kuri prototype" width="618" height="320" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Memory shared by Kuri&#8217;s Robotics Engineer, Hai Nguyen</p></div>
<p>These gifts were thoughtfully designed to introduce you to the history of your Kuri home robot, as well as add unique Kuri touches to your home. We hope you and your family will love hugging this mini stuffed Kuri, and enjoy flipping through the pages of our beautifully crafted Kuri prototype book.</p>
<p>Remember, only customers that place their pre-orders before December 12th will receive these adorable gifts in time for the holidays. If you haven&#8217;t reserved your Kuri yet, you can <a href="https://heykuri.celeryshop.com/checkout?product_id=5907836a3d7c56120053d790&#038;country=us">place your pre-order on our website now</a>. Happy holidays!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/free-gifts-holiday-pre-orders/">Free Gifts for Holiday Pre-Orders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/free-gifts-holiday-pre-orders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>37</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri Entertains with Dance Moves</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=573</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>From morning to night, Kuri fills your home with the sounds that keep you entertained. Kuri has always loved playing music, and now, Kuri is ready to bust a move. Check out the video of Kuri&#8217;s new dance moves! Kuri Dances from KuriRobot on Vimeo. Not only can Kuri play your favorite music, she can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/">Kuri Entertains with Dance Moves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From morning to night, Kuri fills your home with the sounds that keep you entertained. Kuri has always loved playing music, and now, Kuri is ready to bust a move. Check out the video of Kuri&#8217;s <b>new</b> dance moves!</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/259777712?title=0&#038;byline=0" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="https://vimeo.com/259777712">Kuri Dances</a> from <a href="https://vimeo.com/kurirobot">KuriRobot</a> on <a href="https://vimeo.com/">Vimeo</a>.</p>
<p>Not only can Kuri play your favorite music, she can now dance to it with you! When she hears the beat, Kuri will groove along to the beat of any music.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5>Podcasts and Audiobooks Too!</h5>
<p>Coffee with your favorite podcast about robots and space travel? Kuri can do that! Kuri can also read your little one&#8217;s favorite audiobook at bedtime, over and over (and over)… Kuri&#8217;s Bluetooth speakers can play whatever you want to hear most.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-574" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/Kuri-in-the-kitchen-1024x601.jpg" alt="Kuri playing music in the kitchen" width="618" height="363" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5>Powerful Dual Speakers</h5>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-575" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/Kuri-sound.jpg" alt="product picture of Kuri's speaker" width="800" height="516" /></p>
<p>Kuri&#8217;s powerful dual speakers and custom acoustics provide crisp sound that can fill any room with rich sound.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-576" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/Kuri-dance-party.jpg" alt="Kuri dance party with the family" width="1000" height="575" /></p>
<p>Watching Kuri grow into an adorable home robot with a cheerful personality has been an exciting journey. We can&#8217;t wait for you to meet him!</p>
<p>See you on the dance floor!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/">Kuri Entertains with Dance Moves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri Named In Fast Company&#8217;s 2017 Innovation by Design Awards</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-named-in-fast-companys-2017-innovation-by-design-awards/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-named-in-fast-companys-2017-innovation-by-design-awards/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[In the News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=568</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Our team is thrilled to announce that Kuri has been named a finalist in the product category for Fast Company’s 2017 Innovation by Design Awards! With more than 2,500 entries, we&#8217;re proud that our adorable home robot stood out from the pack to have received this distinguished honor. Fast Company&#8216;s Innovation by Design Awards program [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-named-in-fast-companys-2017-innovation-by-design-awards/">Kuri Named In Fast Company&#8217;s 2017 Innovation by Design Awards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our team is thrilled to announce that Kuri has been named a finalist in the product category for <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><i>Fast Company</i></a>’s <a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/innovation-by-design/2017" target="_blank" rel="noopener">2017 Innovation by Design Awards</a>! With more than <b>2,500 entries</b>, we&#8217;re proud that our adorable home robot stood out from the pack to have received this distinguished honor.</p>
<p><i>Fast Company</i>&#8216;s Innovation by Design Awards program (now in its sixth year) honors the most innovative and disruptive design solutions created to resolve today’s most challenging business issues. This year&#8217;s judging panel, comprised of the world’s best design minds, included actor and furniture designer Terry Crews, Kickstarter CEO Yancey Strickler, and Roman Mars, Founder of 99% Invisible.</p>
<p>As a finalist, Kuri is in good company. Featured alongside Coding Awbie, Daydream View, Jamboard, and more — Kuri joins the ranks of <i>Fast Company</i>’s trailblazing products of 2017.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re thrilled that Kuri received a special acknowledgment from an innovative group such as this, and we can’t wait to see how Kuri continues to be received by the world when he starts shipping this December!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-named-in-fast-companys-2017-innovation-by-design-awards/">Kuri Named In Fast Company&#8217;s 2017 Innovation by Design Awards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-named-in-fast-companys-2017-innovation-by-design-awards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri on the Today Show</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-on-the-today-show/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-on-the-today-show/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 21:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[In the News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=509</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you catch Kuri on the Today Show this morning? Kuri had an awesome time twinning with the Today Show’s Stage Manager, meeting Charlie the dog, and sharing her favorite song Pancake Robot with Today Show anchor, Sheinelle Jones. Watch Kuri&#8217;s appearance on the Today Show below! &#160; If you haven&#8217;t already, be sure to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-on-the-today-show/">Kuri on the Today Show</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you catch Kuri on the <a href="https://www.today.com/video/see-kuri-the-friendly-home-robot-visit-the-orange-room-live-1026653251852">Today Show</a> this morning? Kuri had an awesome time twinning with the Today Show’s Stage Manager, meeting Charlie the dog, and sharing her favorite song <i><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o1iOkNDGkFA">Pancake Robot</a></i> with Today Show anchor, Sheinelle Jones. Watch Kuri&#8217;s appearance on the Today Show below!</p>
<div style="width: 960px;" class="wp-video"><!--[if lt IE 9]><script>document.createElement('video');</script><![endif]-->
<video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-509-1" width="960" height="540" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/todayshow_kuri.mp4?_=1" /><a href="https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/todayshow_kuri.mp4">https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/todayshow_kuri.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div id="attachment_510" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://www.today.com/video/see-kuri-the-friendly-home-robot-visit-the-orange-room-live-1026653251852" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img class="size-large wp-image-510" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/Screen-Shot-2017-08-17-at-8.46.52-AM-1024x1024.png" alt="Kuri twinning with the Today Show's Stage Manager, Yosef Herzog" width="618" height="618" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri with Today Show Stage Manager, Yosef Herzog</p></div>
<div id="attachment_512" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://www.today.com/video/see-kuri-the-friendly-home-robot-visit-the-orange-room-live-1026653251852" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img class="wp-image-512 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/DHbmvlGU0AEZC2o-1024x683.jpg" alt="" width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri with Charlie the dog. Photo Credit: Nathan Congleton</p></div>
<div id="attachment_513" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://www.today.com/video/see-kuri-the-friendly-home-robot-visit-the-orange-room-live-1026653251852" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img class="wp-image-513 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/Screen-Shot-2017-08-17-at-8.47.05-AM-1024x627.png" alt="Kuri on the Today Show set" width="618" height="378" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri on the Today Show set</p></div>
<p>If you haven&#8217;t already, be sure to subscribe to Kuri&#8217;s newsletter to hear about upcoming events, meet the team behind Kuri, and more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-on-the-today-show/">Kuri on the Today Show</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-on-the-today-show/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/todayshow_kuri.mp4" length="150224067" type="video/mp4" />
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introducing Kuri Vision: Never Miss a Moment</title>
		<link>/blog/introducing-kuri-vision-never-miss-moment/</link>
		<comments>/blog/introducing-kuri-vision-never-miss-moment/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=463</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Find Kuri in the news: Digital Trends, Money Magazine, and TechCrunch It’s been non-stop robots since we introduced Kuri to the world at CES this year, and since then, we’ve been hard at work fine-tuning Kuri’s hardware and software capabilities&#8211;from adding facial recognition and pet detection, to drivetrain &#38; navigation enhancements, to improving Kuri’s voice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/introducing-kuri-vision-never-miss-moment/">Introducing Kuri Vision: Never Miss a Moment</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>Find Kuri in the news: <a href="https://www.digitaltrends.com/home/kuri-vision-robot-video-camera">Digital Trends</a>, <a href="http://time.com/money/4874972/kuri-robot-800-dollars">Money Magazine</a>, and <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/01/cute-robot-kuri-will-also-work-as-your-family-videographer/?ncid=mobilenavtrend">TechCrunch</a></i></p>
<p class="p1">It’s been non-stop robots since we introduced Kuri to the world at CES this year, and since then, we’ve been hard at work fine-tuning Kuri’s hardware and software capabilities&#8211;from adding facial recognition and pet detection, to drivetrain &amp; navigation enhancements, to improving Kuri’s voice command capabilities and expanding her romojis.</p>
<p class="p1">Now we’re announcing what might be Kuri’s most magical feature: Kuri Vision. Life at home is an extended collection of moments &#8211; some heartfelt, and some hilarious. Kuri can now explore your house and record those valuable moments from your life at home automatically, and even capture moments you might have missed &#8211; from pets daytime antics, to the kids playing together while you’re making dinner.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/225660983?app_id=122963" width="960" height="540" frameborder="0" title="Kuri Vision- Juggling" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p class="p1">Over time, Kuri learns your preferences, too. She&#8217;ll figure out what kind of moments you like best: based on the videos you like within the Kuri app, Kuri will use her image processing and machine learning technology to determine what makes for a good video (according to you), and over time, you’ll start to see that Kuri captures more of the moments you want.</p>
<p class="p1">The real fun is seeing the candid moments she captures for you, letting you build an album of memories without having to pick up your camera. Her unique perspective gives you a magical new view into life&#8217;s memorable moments.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/225661045?app_id=122963" width="960" height="540" frameborder="0" title="Kuri Vision - Family Dance Party" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p class="p1">Part of what makes Kuri Vision possible is Kuri’s deep learning-based computer vision capabilities. This allows Kuri to not only detect people and pets, but to also recognize specific family members.</p>
<p class="p1">Kuri’s app also makes it easy for you to share more of your life at home with your friends and family. Just highlight the videos you want to share, and easily post them to your favorite social channels or messaging apps in just a few quick steps.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-465 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/Kuri-Vision-Dance-Party-1024x500.jpg" alt="" width="618" height="302" /></p>
<p class="p1">Of course, with Kuri Vision, you have complete control over when and where Kuri captures videos. You can designate specific times of the day and locations for her to capture moments, and you can turn this feature off at any time. And like any camera, you’re in control of what happens to the videos, whether you delete them, or share them with the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/introducing-kuri-vision-never-miss-moment/">Introducing Kuri Vision: Never Miss a Moment</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/introducing-kuri-vision-never-miss-moment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri’s got a new trick for pets</title>
		<link>/blog/kuris-got-new-trick-pets/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuris-got-new-trick-pets/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 17:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chris]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=451</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahhh summer. &#160; Happy first official day of cookouts, swimming, sunglasses, and ice cream! Kuri plans to get the summer rolling (pun intended) with a trip to Palm Springs. She’s also got some big updates on her camera, head and eye movements, and drivetrain. And if you have a cat or dog, you’ll want to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-got-new-trick-pets/">Kuri’s got a new trick for pets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h5>Ahhh summer.</h5>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5><b>Happy first</b> official<b> day of cookouts, swimming, sunglasses, and ice cream!</b></h5>
<p>Kuri plans to get the summer rolling (pun intended) with a trip to Palm Springs. She’s also got some big updates on her camera, head and eye movements, and drivetrain. And if you have a cat or dog, you’ll want to read about the awesome new trick Kuri can do.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5><b>Kuri&#8217;s New</b> Pet<b> Trick</b></h5>
<p>Kuri now knows when there&#8217;s a dog or cat in view. This will lead to more adorable pictures and videos, and it allows Kuri to understand that a moving pet and moving person are different from each other. As you can see, the testing in our office for this feature has been doggedly exhausting.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5>Kuri Sees 20/20</h5>
<p>The robo optometrist results are in — Kuri can see in HD. His remarkable 1080p HD camera is now fully complete and integrated, with a precision lens that allows him to get great pictures, videos, and even livestreaming; making it easier to stay connected to your family and your home.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-455 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/camera_news-1-300x195.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="195" /></p>
<p>A peek under the hood shows Kuri&#8217;s camera and circuitry</p>
<p>We knew that Kuri’s nearly magical ability to move around your home wasn’t quite enough to get all the best views, so we made sure he can look around too — just like we do. Kuri can rotate his head left and right, and tilt his head down and upwards, allowing a smooth range of motion that expands his total field of view.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5>Kuri’s Effortless Movements</h5>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-456 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/pinkthing_1024-300x195.png" alt="" width="300" height="195" /></p>
<p class="p1">We’re excited about this one: Kuri’s engineering team has made her drivetrain even more incredible than we originally planned. Instead of traditional drive wheels, Kuri uses a pair of powerful belt treads that provide amazing agility and precision. Kuri&#8217;s movements are now smoother and quieter, and she&#8217;s simultaneously got more traction than ever. Kuri glides from room to room; easily navigating over most rugs and thresholds.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h5>Kuri’s Upcoming Desert Vacation</h5>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-457 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/YxYY-pool-wide-2.png" alt="" width="600" height="200" /></p>
<p class="p1">From July 7-10, Kuri is setting up a robot lounge at the Ace Hotel &amp; Swim Club in Palm Springs, CA for Yes and Yes Yes — a summer retreat for anyone who considers themselves a thinker, maker, creator, nerd, or weirdo. Kuri won’t swim, but he’ll definitely be a part of the inspiration.</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><a href="http://www.yesandyesyes.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Check out what Kuri is getting into here</a>.</span></p>
<p class="p1">Things are really heating up as we get closer and closer to the day when we start shipping Kuri. We have more updates in the works, stay tuned!</p>
<p class="p1">Let the good times roll!</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>&#8211; The Kuri Team</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-got-new-trick-pets/">Kuri’s got a new trick for pets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuris-got-new-trick-pets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Psst. Kuri&#8217;s price goes up June 22. Last chance for intro pricing!</title>
		<link>/blog/psst-kuris-price-goes-june-22-last-chance-intro-pricing/</link>
		<comments>/blog/psst-kuris-price-goes-june-22-last-chance-intro-pricing/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 17:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chris]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=439</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Kuri&#8217;s latest adventures We’ve got some big news and some even bigger news! Read on for the inside scoop on a few upcoming Kuri events (big!), some fresh Kuri hype from the internets (also big!), and a kinda-secret, just-for-Kuri-fans pricing update, plus details on how you can take full advantage of it (super big!). To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/psst-kuris-price-goes-june-22-last-chance-intro-pricing/">Psst. Kuri&#8217;s price goes up June 22. Last chance for intro pricing!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 class="p1"><strong>Kuri&#8217;s latest adventures</strong></h3>
<p class="p1">We’ve got some big news and some even bigger news! Read on for the inside scoop on a few upcoming Kuri events (big!), some fresh Kuri hype from the internets (also big!), and a kinda-secret, just-for-Kuri-fans pricing update, plus details on how you can take full advantage of it (super big!).</p>
<p class="p1">To start things off&#8230;</p>
<p><b>Kuri’s price goes up on June 22 </b></p>
<p class="p2">We’re telling you in advance that we’re raising the price? Crazy, right?</p>
<p class="p2">Nope. 100% not crazy.</p>
<p class="p2">Kuri’s price will be increasing to $799 on June 22nd at 10am PDT.  You were already here with us, so we wanted you to have advance notice. If you place your $100 pre-order deposit before June 22nd, you’ll still get the original $699 price when we ship your robot. It’s our way of saying thanks for being one of our first friends.</p>
<p class="p2">Two very good questions:</p>
<p class="p2"><i>1. Why are we doing this? </i></p>
<p class="p2">Kuri’s going to be even better than we planned. Our engineers found some very clever ways to make Kuri&#8217;s camera, WiFi, and drivetrain even more awesome. All of this introduced a few extra costs, but we know Kuri will be a much better addition to your home, and that’s what matters most.</p>
<p class="p2"><i>2. Does this mean there will be two versions of Kuri?</i></p>
<p class="p2">Nope. There’s only one Kuri. People who place pre-orders before June 22nd will enjoy the original price, and those who order later will pay the (still pretty fantastic) new price, but everyone gets the same incredible robot.</p>
<p class="p2">If you’ve already pre-ordered, you’re already locked in at the $699 price.</p>
<h3><strong>Kuri&#8217;s next open house</strong></h3>
<h4><strong>Calling all robot fans</strong></h4>
<h4 class="p2"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-444 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/Open-House-evite-graphics_Footer-1024x384.jpg" alt="" width="618" height="232" /></h4>
<h4 class="p2"></h4>
<p class="p2">It’s that time again! Do the robot dance with Kuri at our upcoming open house on <b>June 21, from 6:00 &#8211; 8:00 pm</b> at Kuri HQ for an evening of food, festivities, and #RobotLove. We’ll be showing you how Kuri came to be, meet some of our brilliant team, and interact with Kuri in person and see all his recent progress.</p>
<p class="p2">RSVP by giving us your name and how many people are coming, and we’ll get you in. Hurry because spots are limited.</p>
<p class="p4">Click here to <a href="mailto:events@heykuri.com">rsvp</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">Can’t wait to see you there!</p>
<hr />
<h3 class="p2"><strong>Hot off the press</strong></h3>
<h5 class="p2"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-436" src="/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/kuri_docking_optimized.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="400" /></h5>
<p class="p2"><strong>TechCrunch &#8211; Adorable robot friend Kuri can now find its way home to charge</strong></p>
<p>Kuri, the robot companion being developed by startup Mayfield Robotics, is getting closer to production and gaining some new abilities ahead of its planned release later this year. The adorable little bot, which looks like something ripped from a Pixar movie, now does self-charging, topping up his powerhouse when needed. The robot can also map its home environment better, has improved speaker acoustics and more. Please click <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/05/18/adorable-robot-friend-kuri-can-now-find-its-way-home-to-charge/">here</a> to read more.</p>
<h3 class="p2"><b> </b><b>Kuri Experiences High Altitude</b></h3>
<p class="p2"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-446" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/29535107316_9ea4527cea_o.jpg" alt="" width="3300" height="2203" /></p>
<p class="p2">In a few weeks, Kuri heads to Aspen, CO for the <a href="https://www.aspenideas.org/"><span class="s2">Aspen Idea Festival</span></a> on June 29th and 30th. The event will bring public officials, artists, scientists, authors, business executives, scholars, economists, and entrepreneurs together to chat about how to make our world more awesome.</p>
<p class="p2">If you’re attending the festival, you better come say hello! Kuri will be rolling around the Stranahan Room and will be making some surprise cameos around the festival.</p>
<p class="p2">We’ll be sure to share some footage when we’re back.  Stay tuned.</p>
<p class="p2">In a couple weeks, we’ll share more updates on Kuri’s tech improvements. And if you want to know more about the price change, simply hit “reply” to this email and we’ll get back to ya.</p>
<p class="p2">Beep-Beep-Bloop! (“Have a nice weekend”)</p>
<p class="p2">The Kuri Team</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/psst-kuris-price-goes-june-22-last-chance-intro-pricing/">Psst. Kuri&#8217;s price goes up June 22. Last chance for intro pricing!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/psst-kuris-price-goes-june-22-last-chance-intro-pricing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
