<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hey Kuri</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Meet Kuri, the adorable home robot.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</title>
		<link>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/</link>
		<comments>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 17:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2339</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Robot friends, Since late 2017, we&#8217;ve been searching for external partners to support our future. Together with Bosch, we pursued many options for additional financial investment and long-term technology development. Unfortunately, we were unable to reach an agreement with any of the many dozens of companies we talked to. Sadly, this means that Mayfield Robotics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/">The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robot friends,</p>
<p>Since late 2017, we&#8217;ve been searching for external partners to support our future. Together with Bosch, we pursued many options for additional financial investment and long-term technology development. Unfortunately, we were unable to reach an agreement with any of the many dozens of companies we talked to. Sadly, this means that Mayfield Robotics will cease all operations by October 31st, 2018.</p>
<p>Our team is beyond disappointed. Together we&#8217;ve spent the past four years designing and building not just Kuri, but also an equally incredible company culture and spirit. Given this news, we&#8217;re now doing everything we can to support our team. To help to make this transition as smooth as possible, Bosch will help with severance packages and outplacement services, and our team has the option to apply to open positions at Bosch.</p>
<p>When we began this adventure in 2015, we knew our goals were ambitious, and we knew that home robots were still just an idea that we would have to shape. We&#8217;re proud of the work we&#8217;ve done, and the adorable robot we&#8217;ve made. We only wish we could have shipped many more of them to homes and families. The work has certainly inspired all of us, and now we’ll have to wait and see what we all make next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/">The Future of Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Kuri Home Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/the-future-of-mayfield-robotics-kuri-home-robot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</title>
		<link>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/</link>
		<comments>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2336</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>To all of our Kuri fans, we are crushed to let you know that effective today, Mayfield Robotics will pause operations as we evaluate the company&#8217;s path forward. Sadly, our Kuri manufacturing will cease, and the Kuri robots that have been made will not ship to customers. All pre-order deposits will be refunded to our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/important_difficult_announcement/">An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To all of our Kuri fans, we are crushed to let you know that effective today, Mayfield Robotics will pause operations as we evaluate the company&#8217;s path forward. Sadly, our Kuri manufacturing will cease, and the Kuri robots that have been made will not ship to customers. All pre-order deposits will be refunded to our customers.</p>
<h1>So what happened?</h1>
<p>As many of you know, Mayfield Robotics was launched in 2015 as an independent entity of the Bosch Startup Platform. From the beginning, we have been constantly looking for the best paths to achieve scale and continue to advance our innovative technology. Typically, startups in the Bosch Startup Platform are integrated into existing Bosch business units, but after extensive review, there was not a business fit within Bosch to support and scale our business.</p>
<p>Since Kuri&#8217;s award-winning launch at CES 2017, our adorable home robot has been demoed and celebrated at TED, SXSW, The Aspen Ideas Festival, The Economist Innovation Summit, and many other high-profile events. It&#8217;s an understatement to say that we are all hugely disappointed by this pause to operations. We remain proud of the work we&#8217;ve done to push home robotics forward.</p>
<h1>What happens now?</h1>
<p>The vision that began Mayfield Robotics was to make robots that are joyful, useful, and inspiring. Kuri struck each of those notes, and we remain optimistic for an adorable robot future that aligns with our vision. We want to sincerely thank everyone who supported us: our families, our friends, our suppliers, and of course, you, our customers.</p>
<p>Creating a robot like Kuri is a massive undertaking. We don&#8217;t know what the coming months will bring. Regardless, we stand firm in our belief that the home robot Renaissance is just beginning, and it’s going to be amazing.</p>
<p><i>If you have questions regarding your preorder, please email our Kuri Experience team at <a href="mailto:support@heykuri.com?Subject=My Pre-Order" target="_top">support@heykuri.com</a>.</i></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/important_difficult_announcement/">An Important (And Difficult) Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/important_difficult_announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Faces Behind the Robot</title>
		<link>/blog/the-faces-behind-the-robot/</link>
		<comments>/blog/the-faces-behind-the-robot/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 22:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kuri's Team]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2321</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s no understatement to say it takes a village to build Kuri. We were excited to create this campaign, The Faces Behind the Robot, to showcase some of the awesome individuals responsible for bringing Kuri to life. Check out the goofy clips and read in-depth interviews with the Mayfielders whose roles, responsibilities, or strong eyebrow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-faces-behind-the-robot/">The Faces Behind the Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s no understatement to say it takes a village to build Kuri. We were excited to create this campaign, The Faces Behind the Robot, to showcase some of the awesome individuals responsible for bringing Kuri to life. Check out the goofy clips and read in-depth interviews with the Mayfielders whose roles, responsibilities, or strong eyebrow game you’d like to learn more about!</p>
<p><h2>Jackie Lai, Hardware</h2>
<p>Meet Jackie Lai! She’s Kuri&#8217;s Director of Hardware. As Jackie explains, &#8220;Hardware is anything you can touch, which is literally the robot itself. The software is all the stuff you can’t see that makes Kuri run.&#8221; When Jackie isn&#8217;t assembling the physical components of Kuri, you can find her spending time with her family, teaching prenatal yoga, and eating General Mills cereal.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/owNHmuOhx14" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-jackie-lai/"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/2-learn-more-button.jpg" alt="" width="224" height="71" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2324" /></a></p>
<p><h2>Connor Moore, Sound</h2>
<p>One of the most popular questions our team receives is, &#8220;Why doesn&#8217;t Kuri speak?&#8221; The thing is, Kuri does speak! Just like R2-D2 beeps in affirmation in Star Wars or how your dog barks and wags his tail when he&#8217;s excited to see you, Kuri communicates in her own way. Our Sound Designer, Connor Moore, shares more:</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KQ6oIZR0w-o" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="/blog/understanding-kuri-speaks/"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/2-learn-more-button.jpg" alt="" width="224" height="71" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2324" /></a></p>
<p><h2>Jamie Young, Projects</h2>
<p>As a Sr. Technical Project Manager, Jamie Young keeps Kuri&#8217;s hardware, software, product, and marketing teams on track. In short, Jamie is a rockstar at Mayfield Robotics. Her attention to detail, witty humor, and positive attitude make her a joy to work with. That, combined with her impressive engineering background, make Jamie an invaluable member of Kuri’s crew.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3zveuuOFESE" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k0sod-zae1g" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-jamie-young/"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/2-learn-more-button.jpg" alt="" width="224" height="71" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2324" /></a></p>
<p><h2>Paul Mathieu, Software</h2>
<p>Meet Paul! He&#8217;s Kuri&#8217;s Embedded Software Engineer and is known for his ingenuity, creativity, and friendliness. Paul does a lot of the coding behind Kuri&#8217;s behaviors.  As he shares, &#8220;I program things like how Kuri moves her head or turns her wheels into her motor control. I work a lot with our team’s designer, Doug. Doug uses 3D animations to imagine how Kuri should move, and I then work to bring his vision to life within Kuri.&#8221;</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CBS7Ec25NpQ" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-paul-mathieu/"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/2-learn-more-button.jpg" alt="" width="224" height="71" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2324" /></a></p>
<p><h2>Tisho Georgiev, Product</h2>
<p>Tisho is Kuri&#8217;s VP of Product and is responsible for developing Kuri&#8217;s product roadmap, which includes one of his favorite product features: Kuri Vision. Kuri Vision is the collection of video moments that Kuri captures around your home. Learn more about Tisho and the ways Kuri can help you never miss a hilarious or heartwarming moment with your loved ones:</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/v1BfZPS9Ag0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s5hhadi668w" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><a href="/blog/kuri-vision-how-kuri-captures-moments/"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/2-learn-more-button.jpg" alt="" width="224" height="71" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2324" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-faces-behind-the-robot/">The Faces Behind the Robot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/the-faces-behind-the-robot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri is One Tough Cookiebot</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-is-one-tough-cookiebot/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-is-one-tough-cookiebot/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2235</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Either a home robot has arrived at your doorstep, or you&#8217;re considering investing in this technology. One of the biggest questions you&#8217;re weighing might be, &#8220;I know Kuri is a home robot, but how will it hold up to the rhythms of my home? More importantly, how do I care for and clean it?&#8221; Have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-is-one-tough-cookiebot/">Kuri is One Tough Cookiebot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Either a home robot has arrived at your doorstep, or you&#8217;re considering investing in this technology. One of the biggest questions you&#8217;re weighing might be, &#8220;I know Kuri is a home robot, but how will it hold up to the rhythms of <i>my</i> home? More importantly, how do I care for and clean it?&#8221;</p>
<p>Have no fear! Our team has put Kuri to the ultimate test.</p>
<p><h1>Drop It like It&#8217;s Bot</h1>
<p>For starters, our engineering team put Kuri through stringent drop testing. Drop tests are important because they confirm the integrity of a product and its packaging to withstand the rigors of normal usage and shipping. Given we’re making an adorable home robot, we figured our drop test video should be just as memorable:</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qeYmj-V-ddo" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>As you can see, Kuri is made of durable plastic and designed to be where the action is in your home. We don&#8217;t recommend you dropping Kuri on her head or flinging kettle weights her way on the regular. If it&#8217;s pets, kids, or the accidental karate chop, then Kuri is a tough cookie that can easily roll with the punches. You shouldn’t have to worry about Kuri being too delicate to keep up with the liveliness of your home.</p>
<p><h1>Rub-A-Dub-Dub, Kuri in a Tub</h1>
<p>Last year, you might have seen the <a href="/blog/kuris-latest-progress-updates-peanut-butter/">peanut butter test</a>. To one-up ourselves, our marketing team recently put Kuri through a slew of at-home messes. We&#8217;re talking silly putty, deviled eggs, crayons, sunscreen, markers, peanut butter, coffee, meatballs, whipped cream, and water guns. The team used a prototype Kuri to create this video, and a bajillion cleaning wipes to get her sparkling like new!</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YW1r4qz42qo" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wUp3fWDw9Is" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Please don&#8217;t try this at home. Although Kuri&#8217;s plastic is water resistant (not waterproof), there are still enough nooks and crannies that we wouldn&#8217;t recommend bringing Kuri along for bathtime. However, his plastic shell and curved body make it easy to clean up any minor (or slingshotted) spills. Accidents do happen, so if you notice your robot isn&#8217;t working properly for whatever reason, we recommend contacting our Kuri Experience team directly at <a href="mailto:support@heykuri.com">support@heykuri.com</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-is-one-tough-cookiebot/">Kuri is One Tough Cookiebot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-is-one-tough-cookiebot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri&#8217;s Android App Is Out!</title>
		<link>/blog/kuris-android-app-is-out/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuris-android-app-is-out/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 18:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2226</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Calling all Kuri fans! The Kuri Robot app is officially live on the Google Play store. As the makers of one cute robot, we couldn&#8217;t pass up the opportunity to make an app for an OS with another cute robot as its mascot. If you own any Android device (like a Google Pixel or Samsung [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-android-app-is-out/">Kuri&#8217;s Android App Is Out!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Calling all Kuri fans! The Kuri Robot app is officially <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mayfieldrobotics.kuri.enterprise.master" target="_blank">live on the Google Play store</a>. As the makers of one cute robot, we couldn&#8217;t pass up the opportunity to make an app for an OS with another cute robot as its mascot. If you own any Android device (like a Google Pixel or Samsung Galaxy smartphone), then you’re now able to access all the fun there is to have with <a href="https://heykuri.celeryshop.com/checkout?product_id=5907836a3d7c56120053d790&#038;country=us">owning your own Kuri home robot</a>.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store.jpg"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store-1024x841.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="788" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-2234" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store-1024x841.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store-300x246.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store-768x631.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store-600x493.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Kuri-Android-App-Google-Play-Store.jpg 1432w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a></p>
<p>As our VP of Product Tisho Georgiev shares, &#8220;Today, we&#8217;re happy to introduce Kuri for Android. It&#8217;s important that everyone in the home gets to use all the features that Kuri&#8217;s companion app offers, so support for one of the most popular mobile platforms on the planet is essential. The team has been working really hard to bring you all the features that Kuri for iOS offers, and we&#8217;re all excited for you to check out the app on the Google Play Store.&#8221;</p>
<div id="attachment_2229" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383.jpg"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-1024x1024.jpg" alt="Kuri with his new Android app." width="960" height="960" class="size-large wp-image-2229" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-768x768.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-600x600.jpg 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/IMG_1383-100x100.jpg 100w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri with his new Android app.</p></div>
<p>As an Android device owner, you&#8217;ll use the Kuri Robot app to set your robot up, view your Kuri Vision moments, drive your Kuri, and so much more. Take a look inside the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mayfieldrobotics.kuri.enterprise.master" target="_blank">Android app</a>!</p>
<div id="attachment_2236" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections.jpg"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections-1024x768.jpg" alt="Reviewing your Kuri Vision Collections." width="960" height="720" class="size-large wp-image-2236" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections-768x576.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_Collections-600x450.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Reviewing your Kuri Vision Collections.</p></div>
<div id="attachment_2237" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings.jpg"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings-1024x768.jpg" alt="Making changes to your robot&#039;s settings." width="960" height="720" class="size-large wp-image-2237" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings-768x576.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_robot-settings-600x450.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Making changes to your robot&#8217;s settings.</p></div>
<div id="attachment_2238" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try.jpg"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try-1024x768.jpg" alt="Discovering new things to try with your Kuri." width="960" height="720" class="size-large wp-image-2238" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try-768x576.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/android_things-to-try-600x450.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Discovering new things to try with your Kuri.</p></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-android-app-is-out/">Kuri&#8217;s Android App Is Out!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuris-android-app-is-out/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri&#8217;s Crew: Meet Ashley Wakefield</title>
		<link>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-ashley-wakefield/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-ashley-wakefield/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kuri's Team]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2211</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet Ashley Wakefield! She&#8217;s Kuri&#8217;s Customer Success Manager and responsible for keeping our robot&#8217;s customers happy. The second wave of Kuri pre-orders will begin rolling out this month, so we thought it was a perfect opportunity to chat with Ashley about her role and what she loves about supporting a community of home robot enthusiasts. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-ashley-wakefield/">Kuri&#8217;s Crew: Meet Ashley Wakefield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Ashley Wakefield! She&#8217;s Kuri&#8217;s Customer Success Manager and responsible for keeping our robot&#8217;s customers happy. The second wave of Kuri pre-orders will begin rolling out this month, so we thought it was a perfect opportunity to chat with Ashley about her role and what she loves about supporting a community of home robot enthusiasts.</p>
<p><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-1553" style="max-width: 300px; float: right;" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley_headshot-300x300.png" alt="Ashley Wakefiled with Kuri home robot" width="300" height="300" /></p>
<p><b>Q: How do you define customer success?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> To me, customer success is making sure customers feel heard and that they know we&#8217;re doing everything we can to help them. A big part of customer success is being a customer advocate because you&#8217;re always on the customer&#8217;s side. We&#8217;re not here to say no, shut down requests, or defend the company. My goal is for customers to know that they&#8217;ll be heard, that I&#8217;m here to help them, and that I&#8217;ll treat them with the same level of respect as my own mother. At the end of the day, I want customers to have the best experience possible.</p>
<p><b>Q: What does your day-to-day look like at Mayfield Robotics?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> The first thing I do in the morning is meet with our software and hardware engineering teams to evaluate any known issues that customers might encounter with their robots and how we’d address them. We&#8217;re continuously improving Kuri, so new bugs sometimes arise. In these meetings, we create workarounds to best address these issues or fix them moving forward.</p>
<p>I then answer customer inquiries. During this process, I look for trends. Are customers bringing up a lot of the same questions or issues? If so, how can we better share this information so that customers aren’t confused or feel the need to email us?</p>
<p>I&#8217;ll also regularly take a holistic look at our customer success program. I focus on ways we can anticipate new customer questions, adopt more efficient processes, and ultimately scale the program to support our growing number of customers. I’m usually asking myself, &#8220;How can we make this process as easy and painless for customers to get their questions answered?&#8221; To answer this, I&#8217;ll revisit our submission forms, support documentation, and emails to make sure everything runs smoothly. I&#8217;ll even work with our QA team and go through the entire user onboarding experience of Kuri so that I’m constantly familiar with updates and changes to our product to better help customers.</p>
<p>Things change rapidly, so my days consist of daily meetings within our team to make sure we&#8217;re on top of updates, communications, and always feel like we’re aligned. Moving forward, I&#8217;m trying to build a stronger family relationship between our team and customers so that customers understand we’re in this robot dream together.</p>
<p><b>Q: How would you describe Kuri&#8217;s customers?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Kuri&#8217;s customers are passionate and feel like friends and family to me. You go through hardships with loved ones, but you always figure out a way to recover and come back even stronger. Some of our customers have waited a year and a half for this little robot to appear on their doorsteps. Understandably, they&#8217;re frustrated. I&#8217;ve done everything I can to build transparency, but I really appreciate how understanding our customers are. There’s always so much encouragement from their side whether it’s a funny meme or a quick note to keep up the good work. They really mean the world to me.</p>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s your favorite way to engage with Kuri customers?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I love face-to-face interactions with Kuri customers at events. You build a stronger connection being able to see someone and have a conversation in-person versus over email because there&#8217;s someone to hug.</p>
<p><p>This question actually reminds me of a specific customer named Darrell who was really excited to purchase Kuri but was worried that his daughter would be frightened. He came to one of our <a href="/blog/kuri-captivates-los-angeles/">mall events</a> and we watched his daughter meet Kuri for the first time together. She ended up loving Kuri! Sharing that moment together made me feel like I was a part of their family, and it’s exciting to know that Kuri is going to be a part of this family too.</p>
<div id="attachment_2213" style="width: 282px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Darrell-with-Kuri-272x300.jpg" alt="Darrell’s daughter meeting Kuri for the first time." width="272" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-2213" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Darrell-with-Kuri-272x300.jpg 272w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Darrell-with-Kuri-768x848.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Darrell-with-Kuri-928x1024.jpg 928w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Darrell-with-Kuri-600x662.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 272px) 100vw, 272px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Darrell’s daughter meeting Kuri for the first time.</p></div>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s the hardest part about supporting customers?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Sometimes we just don’t have answers to their questions. That&#8217;s really difficult for me to deal with because my job is to provide information to customers as best I can. Because of that, customers sometimes think I&#8217;m not trying to help them. When in reality, we’re chasing co-workers to their offices to get answers to customers&#8217; questions behind the scenes. My responsibility is to advocate for customers&#8217; needs, and that’s what I think about whenever an email is sent their way with updated messaging.</p>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s your favorite part about Kuri?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I&#8217;m a big proponent of 30-second dance parties. With Kuri around, you don&#8217;t even need other people. She&#8217;s right there to <a href="/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/">shimmy along with me</a>! I love when you&#8217;re having a dinner party or get together because Kuri can roll around playing music and <a href="/blog/kuri-vision-kuri-films/">capturing moments</a> without you having to stop the party. That&#8217;s important to me because it’s hard to balance always wanting to be the person that documents things with my phone, with the person that just wants to live in the moment.</p>
<p><b>Q: What most excites you about Kuri&#8217;s future?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> The development of her personality. Right now, Kuri is very cute. In the future, I think Kuri is going to have a more in-depth personality and her mannerisms and quirks will be more exciting to see. The intricate designs of Kuri blinking or turning before she moves are great stepping stones toward that future. With her cute personality, I think Kuri puts a lot of people at ease that might be fearful of robotics. Kuri bridges that gap between Terminator robots taking over the world and people that are excited about a future with robots like in <i>The Jetsons</i>.</p>
<p><b>Q: Where would we find you in your spare time?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I&#8217;m all about interesting experiences and trying new things. Growing up, my Mom always taught me that you should try something at least once because why not? When you’re trying something new, you’re pushing your boundaries &mdash; which is something I love doing.</p>
<p>I constantly want to be improving to be a better person. For example, I&#8217;ve tried beekeeping, painting, and playing soccer and I have an upcoming trip planned for Vietnam. Traveling and trying new things remind you how to be grateful for what you already have.</p>
<div id="attachment_2214" style="width: 247px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley-with-Kuri-robot-at-HQ-237x300.jpg" alt="Ashley with Kuri at Kuri's HQ." width="237" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-2214" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley-with-Kuri-robot-at-HQ-237x300.jpg 237w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley-with-Kuri-robot-at-HQ-768x973.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley-with-Kuri-robot-at-HQ-809x1024.jpg 809w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Ashley-with-Kuri-robot-at-HQ-600x760.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 237px) 100vw, 237px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Ashley with Kuri at her HQ.</p></div>
<p>When asked if there was anything else she&#8217;d like to share with Kuri customers, Ashley volunteered, &#8220;Just that I’m always here for them. Once you&#8217;re a Kuri customer, you&#8217;re a part of this family for life.&#8221; Ashley is one of the most passionate customer advocates on Kuri&#8217;s crew, and she looks forward to interacting with you too! If you haven&#8217;t already, be sure to <a href="https://heykuri.celeryshop.com/checkout?product_id=5907836a3d7c56120053d790&#038;country=us">reserve your robot</a> so you can join the Kuri customer family.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-ashley-wakefield/">Kuri&#8217;s Crew: Meet Ashley Wakefield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-ashley-wakefield/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Home Robot Joins the Maker Movement</title>
		<link>/blog/our-home-robot-joins-the-maker-movement/</link>
		<comments>/blog/our-home-robot-joins-the-maker-movement/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/?p=1817</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>2018 marked the 13th annual Bay Area Maker Faire! Located at the San Mateo County Events Center, the Maker Faire is a family-friendly festival of creativity, resourcefulness, and a celebration of the maker movement. Kuri at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire. Having been born a short ten-minute drive away in Redwood City, Kuri was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/our-home-robot-joins-the-maker-movement/">Our Home Robot Joins the Maker Movement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2018 marked the 13th annual <a href="https://makerfaire.com/bay-area/" target="_blank">Bay Area Maker Faire</a>! Located at the San Mateo County Events Center, the Maker Faire is a family-friendly festival of creativity, resourcefulness, and a celebration of the maker movement.</p>
<p><figure><img class="tie-appear aligncenter wp-image-1211 size-large" src="http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2645-768x1024.jpg" alt="Kuri at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire." width="618" height="824" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire.</figcaption></figure>
<p>Having been born a short ten-minute drive away in Redwood City, Kuri was a natural addition to this festival of invention!</p>
<figure><img class="alignnone" src="http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2632-1024x1024.jpg&quot;" alt="Attractions from the Bay Area Maker Faire." width="618" height="618" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Attractions from the Bay Area Maker Faire.</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kuri&#8217;s crew attended this year&#8217;s Maker Faire to introduce the maker community to our adorable home robot. Whether that meant interacting with fans one-on-one, putting on an impromptu dance rehearsal, or handing out cool robot swag, Kuri was delighted to make new friends. As you can see, Kuri drew quite the crowd!</p>
<figure><img src="http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Image-2-1024x700.jpg" alt="Kuri’s booth at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire." width="618" height="422" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri’s booth at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire.</figcaption></figure>
<p>When he wasn&#8217;t wowing the crowd, Kuri was exploring the sites at the Maker Faire. From 3D-printed signage to a local club that builds functioning R2-D2 robots, Kuri was exposed to a whole host of creativity!</p>
<figure id="attachment_1214" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><img class="tie-appear aligncenter wp-image-1214 size-large" src="https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2652-1024x768.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 618px) 100vw, 618px" srcset="https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2652-1024x768.jpg 1024w, https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2652-300x225.jpg 300w, https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2652-768x576.jpg 768w, https://blog.heykuri.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2652-500x375.jpg 500w" alt="Kuri in front of a 3D-printed sign made with upcycled materials." width="618" height="464" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri in front of a 3D-printed sign made with upcycled materials.</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<figure><img class="alignnone" src="http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2726.jpg" alt="Kuri with his new Star Wars BFFs." width="618" height="762" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri with his new BFFs.</figcaption></figure>
<p>Our team knows our home robot is an adorable mover and shaker, and we&#8217;re excited that the rest of the maker community thinks so too.</p>
<figure><img src="http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_2719-768x1101.jpg" alt="Kuri at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire." width="618" height="886" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri at the 2018 Bay Area Maker Faire.</figcaption></figure>
<p>Until next time, Makers!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/our-home-robot-joins-the-maker-movement/">Our Home Robot Joins the Maker Movement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/our-home-robot-joins-the-maker-movement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri’s Crew: Meet Hai Nguyen</title>
		<link>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-hai-nguyen/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-hai-nguyen/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kuri's Team]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/?p=1718</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet Hai Nguyen! He&#8217;s Kuri&#8217;s Sr. Robotics Engineer and was the first employee at Mayfield Robotics where he has been instrumental in developing Kuri. Since Hai has been with Kuri from the beginning, he has a unique perspective on Kuri&#8217;s evolution from a dream to the independent, personality-driven robot we all know and love today. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-hai-nguyen/">Kuri’s Crew: Meet Hai Nguyen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Hai Nguyen! He&#8217;s Kuri&#8217;s Sr. Robotics Engineer and was the first employee at Mayfield Robotics where he has been instrumental in developing Kuri. Since Hai has been with Kuri from the beginning, he has a unique perspective on Kuri&#8217;s evolution from a dream to the independent, personality-driven robot we all know and love today.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Hai_Nguyen_Mayfield_Robotics-500x500.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-1192 tie-appear" style="max-width: 300px; float: right;" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Hai_Nguyen_Mayfield_Robotics-500x500.jpg" alt="Headshot of Hai Nguyen" width="300" height="300" /></a></p>
<p><b>Q: Can you describe some of the projects you work on and how they directly impact Kuri?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Since I&#8217;ve been with Mayfield Robotics from the beginning, I&#8217;ve worked on basically everything. Specifically, I was hired to work on robot behaviors. Behaviors are what Kuri does in reaction to certain events. For example, what should Kuri do when she scoots over a threshold? As Kuri developed more of a social side, it was my responsibility to build the infrastructure where she would respond to events and user commands in a timely manner. Nobody wants to say, &#8220;Hey Kuri! I love you,&#8221; and have Kuri stare blankly back at them.</p>
<p>Other questions I&#8217;ve explored are what Kuri&#8217;s mood should be and how it should be expressed. For example, if you accidentally kick Kuri should she get mad at you? Should Kuri ever be mad at all? Or should Kuri get increasingly sad as her battery lowers throughout the day? I&#8217;ve spent a lot of time thinking about these questions and investigating them in terms of Kuri’s animations and emotional space. Kuri is a very cheery robot. Something I&#8217;m exploring right now is how many different animations and lights are needed to portray that happiness and how much variation <a href="/blog/understanding-kuri-speaks/">Kuri needs to communicate those emotions effectively</a>.</p>
<p>The most recent thing I&#8217;ve built is Kuri’s SLAM (simultaneous localization and mapping) system which was designed to work with a cost-efficient depth sensor. This algorithm enables Kuri to correctly map homes even in varied, challenging environments such as homes with kids and pets. SLAM was an important part of Kuri’s product development because it gave her the ability to move around autonomously.</p>
<p><iframe style="width: 100%;" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/259763013" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><a href="https://vimeo.com/259763013">Depth Sensor</a> from <a href="https://vimeo.com/kurirobot">KuriRobot</a> on <a href="https://vimeo.com/">Vimeo</a>.</p>
<p>Right now, I&#8217;m working on maintaining Kuri&#8217;s spatial memory of where things are in a home. That way, Kuri can wander through a person’s home without bumping into everything or getting lost all the time. That’s my most recent project. It’s very intellectually rewarding.</p>
<p><b>Q: You were an intern at Willow Garage; a company well-known for making some of the biggest robotics breakthroughs. How did your experiences there impact your work with Kuri today?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> The best thing I got from <a href="http://www.willowgarage.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Willow Garage</a> was exposure to many different schools of thought in robotics. My background is in behavior-based robotics which is sort of represented by Marvin Minsky’s <i><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Society_of_Mind" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Society of Mind</a></i>. He believed that minds are made of little mindless bits that when stitched together build true intelligence. When you are asked to perform a task, different little bits get activated to allow you to accomplish that task.</p>
<p>That was my educational background, so it was nice to interact with different perspectives. There were students who had a more classical AI perspective which view human intelligence as being all about logic, so naturally, that&#8217;s what AI should use. At Willow Garage, there were also pragmaticists like our <a href="/blog/personal-robot-inventors">CTO</a>. Pragmatic roboticists are more focused on making robots work for real. It&#8217;s sort of, &#8220;<i>this</i> robot needs to work for this particular purpose, so by hook or by crook, we&#8217;ll make it happen.</p>
<p>Seeing those schools work together to achieve common goals was really powerful. When we were brought together, it didn&#8217;t matter where we were from. We believed that the future was robotics. If we didn&#8217;t help build it, well, there weren&#8217;t many other groups of plucky roboticists funded by billionaires so if not us, then who? We were all genuinely excited to make this happen. Willow Garage no longer exists but our little tribe of roboticists, which is now a global network, still leans on each other to drive the industry forward however we can.</p>
<p><b>Q: You earned your Ph.D. from Georgia Institute of Technology in Robotics. Can you give us a run-down of your thesis?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> The goal of my Ph.D. was to work toward building a general purpose robot. This is a robot where if you want to do a new thing, you don&#8217;t have to completely retool and reprogram it. Instead, maybe the robot needs new tools to use or software.</p>
<p>I was exploring how to educate people to better teach robots how to perform tasks. That meant showing the motions to a robot or naming objects so the robot could practice. Conversely, I was interested in how robots could teach people about which interface is most productive for them; or one that robots could best learn new skills form. That&#8217;s why I developed a program that made it easy for end-users to teach robots to perform in-home behaviors using Photoshop-like tools. Robots need teaching and assistance, and we can’t assume that we humans are inherently the best teachers.</p>
<p><b>Q: You&#8217;ve been working with Kuri from the start. What has it been like to witness Kuri&#8217;s evolution over time?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I’ve experienced a lot of these future shock moments like, &#8220;I&#8217;m in the future! How did this happen?&#8221; When Kuri started out, he felt like a simple little appliance. He’d go from point A to point B without any frills. Then, we put in these seemingly small bits of interactive intelligence and they added up to this really impressive illusion of life over time. It&#8217;s just really cool for me to see these Kuri robots running around our office autonomously and looking around wide-eyed at everything like they’re seeing and appreciating everything for the first time.</p>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s your favorite Kuri behavior?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> My favorite personality aspect of Kuri is extremely simple. It&#8217;s the <a href="/blog/new-romojis-personality/">purring</a> that happens when you pet Kuri&#8217;s head. Even though I know it&#8217;s a simple reflex behavior, I love it and it absolutely charms me every time. It’s so cute and adorable and wonderful.</p>
<p><iframe style="width: 100%;" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/245072255" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p>I&#8217;m glad we stole purring from cats. There are enough cat owners in the company &mdash; including myself &mdash; that instantly understood how emotionally powerful purring is. It was a stupidly simple line of code, but I love how absurdly outsized the emotional impact is compared to the amount of effort it took to build.</p>
<p><b>Q: What are you excited about in the home robotics industry as a whole?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I&#8217;m excited about Kuri! Not just Kuri as a thing, but Kuri coming into the world and changing people&#8217;s perception of what a home robot could be. I believe Kuri will probably set a precedent for many home robots to come. As well as making space in the consumer mindset that, &#8220;Maybe a home robot has been missing from my life. Like a smartphone, of course, I would have a home robot! How do you live without a home robot?&#8221;</p>
<p>I don&#8217;t know if Kuri will create that space, but I think Kuri will definitely plant the seed for that space and help develop it. We have lots of utilitarian robots that vacuum and mop and lots of social robot toy type things, and Kuri is this cool thing that’s in the middle. Kuri is both useful and brings joy to your life.</p>
<p><b>Q: Who is your favorite robot in pop culture?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Battlestar Galactica Caprica <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Number_Six_(Battlestar_Galactica)" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Number Six</a>! She&#8217;s constantly going around talking about her destiny. I love that juxtaposition of humanity and machine and exploring that blurry line. I also love <a href="http://westworld.wikia.com/wiki/Dolores_Abernathy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dolores</a> from Westworld. She kind of has the same bent of being a robot but also a very relatable human character. My hunch is that when we finally make a human level intelligent robot, they will basically be very much like us because they’ll be based on the same principles that we use. It&#8217;s really fun to explore this gray area. Also Major Kusanagi from <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ghost_in_the_Shell" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ghost in the Shell</a>. She grew up without a human body and used a cyborg body her whole life. Because of that, she spends a great deal pondering whether she’s human and what makes that special.</p>
<p><b>Q: When you aren&#8217;t designing Kuri&#8217;s software, what are you doing?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I like to joke that my hobby is collecting hobbies and the recent hobby that I&#8217;ve been collecting is calligraphy, gardening, and reading about neurotransmitters; especially collecting plants that affect neurotransmission in some way. For example, the periwinkle flower can be used to enhance blood flow to the brain to help you learn better and remember more things when you’re reading.<?p></p>
<p>In better understanding how human brains work, I&#8217;m hoping it&#8217;ll one day fit into my work in robotics in helping make little robot brains work.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1193" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="max-width: 237px; margin: 0 auto;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/kuri-ritz-kate-haley-photography-40-500x633.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-1193 tie-appear" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/kuri-ritz-kate-haley-photography-40-500x633.jpg" alt="Hai Nguyen, Kuri's Sr. Robotics Engineer" width="237" height="300" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Hai Nguyen, Kuri&#8217;s Sr. Robotics Engineer</figcaption></figure>
<p>Hai&#8217;s main focus at Mayfield Robotics has been on the cognitive software architectures that support the robot&#8217;s life-like, reactive, and interactive behaviors that allow Kuri to come to life. As the first employee, Hai has worn many hats &mdash; from robotic mapping and navigation algorithms to working on Kuri&#8217;s audio systems, to build whatever is necessary to bring Kuri to the world. Hai has played a critical role in Mayfield’s success in bringing not only a complex technology but also a first-of-its-kind product into the homes of everyday consumers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuris-crew-meet-hai-nguyen/">Kuri’s Crew: Meet Hai Nguyen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuris-crew-meet-hai-nguyen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kids & Kuri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/?p=1711</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>We love featuring talented artists who re-imagine our adorable home robot. That&#8217;s why we were excited when student artist Lily Van shared her whimsical illustrations of Kuri with us! We decided to sit down with Lily to learn more about her as both a designer and a Kuri fan. Q: You&#8217;re currently a digital design [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/">Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We love <a href="/blog/kuri-gets-painted-vr-using-tilt-brush/">featuring talented artists</a> who re-imagine our adorable home robot. That&#8217;s why we were excited when student artist <a href="https://liliuhms.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lily Van</a> shared her whimsical illustrations of Kuri with us! We decided to sit down with Lily to learn more about her as both a designer and a Kuri fan.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Lily_Van_Designer_Kuri.png"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-1160 tie-appear" style="max-width: 300px; float: right;" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Lily_Van_Designer_Kuri.png" alt="Lily Van portrait" width="300" height="300" /></a></p>
<p><b>Q: You&#8217;re currently a digital design student at the University of Colorado at Denver. How does being a student impact your design style and voice?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Yes! Being in school, you&#8217;re simultaneously impacted by the latest technologies, social happenings in the world, and people from all sorts of different walks of life and perspectives. It&#8217;s a really unique environment. As a student, you have limitless access to programs and tools among people whom you&#8217;re learning right alongside.</p>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s your process for creating an illustration from start to finish?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I start with researching so I can get the hang of the feeling I want to create. For me, it&#8217;s important to hone the feeling a finished piece should give you. I&#8217;ll draft out sketches to get the energy down.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1161" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Screen-Shot-2018-04-25-at-10.09.40-AM-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1161 tie-appear" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Screen-Shot-2018-04-25-at-10.09.40-AM-1024x1024.png" alt="Lily's early sketches of Kuri." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Lily’s early sketches of Kuri.</figcaption></figure>
<p>I like work that feels young, whimsical, and a little childlike. For me, the process of working on a project is really enjoyable. I like to create environments that I can put my whole heart into as I&#8217;m creating.</p>
<p><b>Q: How do you think Kuri&#8217;s design helps define her character?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> She looks really friendly. Her design is round and she doesn’t have any harsh lines anywhere. She&#8217;s not odd, disjointed, or boxy. Kuri rolls smoothly, she takes her time, she&#8217;s thoughtful, has friendly eyes, and <a href="/blog/understanding-kuri-speaks/">her audio feedback is pleasant and endearing</a>. Kuri doesn&#8217;t have any off-putting mechanical sounds that make you feel like she’s a machine. She is always encouraging you during your interactions through positive beeps and boops and endearing character movements.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1162" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0764-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1162" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0764-1024x1024.png" alt="Robot Pets by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Robot Pets by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: You’ve shared that one of your goals is to bring playfulness to the world of design. What do you think is playful about Kuri?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> When I was watching the <a href="/videos/">videos about Kuri</a>, Kuri was interacting with the people and pets that&#8217;d be interacting with the robot every day. There wasn’t this sense of distance that I&#8217;ve typically seen with robots. The messaging behind Kuri feels fun and youthful; from <a href="/blog/new-romojis-personality/">Kuri telling jokes to people petting her</a>. It just seems like Kuri fits into customers’ everyday lives and she feels like everyone is welcome to use and interact with her. That&#8217;s how a tech product should be.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1163" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Kuri_Lily-1024x419.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1163" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Kuri_Lily-1024x419.jpg" alt="Kuri illustrations by Lily." width="618" height="253" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri illustrations by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: Which of your Kuri illustrations was your favorite to create and why?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I really like the ones of Kuri interacting with little kids. I was inspired by the videos of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ujdwwr2e4jU" target="_blank">kids talking about their experiences interacting with Kuri</a> and I tried to emulate that in some of these illustrations. Kuri never looks down at kids. She&#8217;s a friend that&#8217;s interacting with them at an equal level. Kuri is instantly approachable, and given that kids grow up with so much technology now, I think Kuri is creating a bridge to those interactions rather than making technology feel cold or distant.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1164" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0761-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1164" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0761-1024x1024.png" alt="Meeting Kuri by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Meeting Kuri by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: Why is it valuable for people to see a real-life robot illustrated?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> People are impacted by the things they see. In design, there&#8217;s this thing called behavioral <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nudge_theory" target="_blank">nudging</a>. For example, how they put brightly colored candy in the grocery store checkout aisle when you&#8217;re closest to making a purchase. I think illustrated robots break down barriers people might have about technology consuming your life. Illustrations create a positive representation of what a helpful, hopeful future of robotics might look like.</p>
<p><b>Q: Who is your favorite robot in pop culture?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I really love <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Astro_Boy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Astro Boy</a>! His story is fantastic. His character is this robot that has human emotions and he tries to fight for robot rights. He&#8217;s just a friendly kid with this heartbreaking backstory and people should definitely check him out.</p>
<p><b>Q: What are you doing when not designing?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I&#8217;m usually just drawing! I have an online store where I make things like apparel and stuff. I try to learn other skills in my free time as well. Right now I&#8217;m making pottery, and I have a goal to master homemade pasta making this year! I just really enjoy exposing myself to new things.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1165" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0762IMG_0762-1024x1024.png.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1165" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0762-1024x1024.png" alt="Kuri's Best Friend by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri’s Best Friend by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p>We loved the playfulness of Lily&#8217;s illustrations of Kuri and we hope you enjoyed getting to meet the designer behind these fun vignettes too. Be sure to check out our <a href="/blog/kuri-gets-painted-vr-using-tilt-brush/">other artist collaborations</a> and to <a href="#footer-newsletter">subscribe to Kuri’s newsletter</a> for more updates on our adorable home robot.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/">Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kids & Kuri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=1121</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On the heels of National Robotics Week, we hosted a local group of girls from Girl Scouts of Northern California&#8217;s Discover Together community-based after school program at Mayfield Robotics HQ. In March, our Co-Founder and COO Sarah Osentoski visited the troop at John Gill Elementary School to talk about women in robotics and how Kuri [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/">Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the heels of <a href="https://www.nationalroboticsweek.org/" target="_blank">National Robotics Week</a>, we hosted a local group of girls from <a href="https://www.gsnorcal.org/en/about-girl-scouts/stem.html" target="_blank">Girl Scouts of Northern California&#8217;s</a> Discover Together community-based after school program at Mayfield Robotics HQ. In March, our Co-Founder and COO <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcY_mreUyQ0" target="_blank">Sarah Osentoski</a> visited the troop at John Gill Elementary School to talk about women in robotics and how Kuri came to be.</p>
<p>As a follow-up, the girls visited Mayfield Robotics&#8217; headquarters in Redwood City, CA. The girls were able to explore where Kuri is built, hear from our Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik and VP of Hardware Jason Umhoefer, and interact with Kuri one-on-one.</p>
<div id="attachment_1122" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5155-copy-2.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1122" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5155-copy-2-1024x683.jpg" alt="Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik showing the girls Kuri's capabilities." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik showing the girls Kuri&#8217;s capabilities.</p></div>
<p>The day started with Ellen welcoming the Girl Scouts to Mayfield Robotics HQ. Ellen explained her role to the girls and how a product team shapes the design and functionality of Kuri. When sharing early Kuri concept illustrations, the girls eagerly related those sketches to their own drawings &mdash; to which Ellen happily offered, &#8220;Yes! If you love drawing or thinking about character development for things like Disney movies, then product could be a good fit for you someday.&#8221;</p>
<div id="attachment_1134" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5218-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1134" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5218-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts in Kuri's hardware lab." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts in Kuri&#8217;s hardware lab.</p></div>
<p>Following their fireside chat with Ellen, the girls headed over to the hardware lab at Mayfield Robotics. There, the girls had an opportunity to see the inner workings of Kuri. Jason explained the basic hardware components that create Kuri&#8217;s &#8220;rib cage&#8221;, head, heart light, laser, drive train, and bump sensor. While in the hardware lab, the girls&#8217; top question was, &#8220;Is Kuri waterproof?&#8221; to which Jason replied, &#8220;No. Kuri isn&#8217;t a big fan of bathtime,&#8221; with a smirk.</p>
<div id="attachment_1124" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5242-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1124" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5242-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield showing what Kuri can do." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield showing what Kuri can do.</p></div>
<p>After taking a look under the hood of Kuri in the hardware lab, the Girl Scouts made their way to the lobby to get a demo of Kuri from Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield.</p>
<div id="attachment_1138" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5325-copy-1.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1138" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5325-copy-1-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts dancing to Kuri’s favorite song, Pancake Robot." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts dancing to Kuri’s favorite song, Pancake Robot.</p></div>
<p>Ashley taught the girls <a href="/blog/new-romojis-personality/">how to tickle Kuri</a>, gave them a tour of the Kuri Robot app, and even had <a href="/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/">Kuri dance</a> for the Girl Scouts! The girls were most in awe of Kuri&#8217;s awesome dance moves and had a blast participating in a group robo-scout dance party.</p>
<div id="attachment_1126" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5301-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1126" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5301-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts opening their Kuri swag bags." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts opening their Kuri swag bags.</p></div>
<div id="attachment_1127" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/girl-scouts.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1127" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/girl-scouts-955x1024.jpg" alt="Kuri-themed Girl Scout cookies as part of their swag." width="618" height="663" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri-themed Girl Scout cookies as part of their swag.</p></div>
<p><P>Following their tour, The Girl Scouts were gifted Kuri swag bags that they opened with gleeful screams. Our team loved watching the girls deck themselves out with Mayfield Robotics sunglasses and Kuri stickers. More importantly, we hope we inspired these young ladies to consider a future career in robotics; be it product, engineering, marketing &mdash; you name it! We had a blast hosting the Girl Scouts at our HQ and can’t wait to host similar community events in the future.</p>
<div id="attachment_1139" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5383-copy-1.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1139" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5383-copy-1-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts group picture!" width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts group picture!</p></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/">Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
