<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Press Releases &#8211; Hey Kuri</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/press-releases/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Meet Kuri, the adorable home robot.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Kuri Launches at CES 2017</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-launches-at-ces-2017/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-launches-at-ces-2017/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chris]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://mayfieldblog.afsbstage.com/?p=26</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>At Mayfield Robotics, we’re all about robots. Collectively, our team has worked on telepresence robots, solar panel robots, agriculture robots, security robots, industrial robots, service and delivery robots, robot software, and more. We’re science and technology nerds and like many of you, we’ve been dreaming of having our own personal robot at home for as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-launches-at-ces-2017/">Kuri Launches at CES 2017</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At Mayfield Robotics, we’re all about robots. Collectively, our team has worked on telepresence robots, solar panel robots, agriculture robots, security robots, industrial robots, service and delivery robots, robot software, and more. We’re science and technology nerds and like many of you, we’ve been dreaming of having our own personal robot at home for as long as we can remember.</p>
<p>Today, we’re excited to share what we’ve quietly been working on for the past two years. His name is Kuri, and he’s a smart, adorable robot for the home designed to have personality, awareness, and mobility. We’ve fallen in love with him, and we think you will too.</p>
<div id="attachment_141" style="width: 490px" class="wp-caption alignright"><img class="wp-image-141 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Blog-Child-Greets-Kuri.jpg" alt="Kuri, the home robot, kissed by child" width="480" height="530" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Child&#8217;s reaction upon meeting Kuri for the first time</p></div>
<h1>Kuri &#8211; A First-of-Its-Kind Home Robot Announced at 2017 International Consumer Electronics Show (CES).</h1>
<h3>Designed with personality, awareness, and mobility, Kuri enhances life at home and helps people connect</h3>
<p>Las Vegas, NV (January 3, 2017) &#8212; Mayfield Robotics , a Bosch startup out of Redwood City, CA, today at CES proudly unveiled Kuri, an intelligent robot for the home. Kuri is designed with personality, awareness, and mobility, and adds a spark of life to any home. Priced at $699, Kuri is available for pre-order in the U.S. with a $100 deposit starting today at heykuri.com.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-140" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/PHOTOS-Kuri_Inspires-at-CES.jpg" alt="Kuri Home Robot Announced at CES" width="621" height="450" /></p>
<p>Kuri is built to connect with you and helps bring technology to life. Kuri can understand context and surroundings,recognize specific people, and respond to questions with facial expressions, head movements, and his unique lovable sounds. Like many adored robots in popular culture, his personality and ability to connect are his greatest attributes.</p>
<p>“For generations, people have dreamed of having their own personal robot in the home, and we’ve been focused on making that dream more of a reality,” said Sarah Osentoski, COO and co-founder of Mayfield Robotics. “We’re proud to introduce Kuri to the world and can’t wait to see how he touches the lives of everyone, ranging from parents and children to early technology adopters.”</p>
<p>Behind his clean design, Kuri is powered by serious hardware &amp; capabilities:</p>
<ul>
<li>A built-in 1080p camera so you can check-in on the house or pets while you’re away;</li>
<li>A 4-Microphone array, powerful dual speakers, and wifi + Bluetooth connectivity, so he can play music, read the kids a bedtime story, or follow you around playing podcasts while you’re getting ready for work;</li>
<li>Various sensors for mapping and detecting edges and objects so he knows where he is, and so you don’t have to worry about him bumping into that chair you forgot to put away, or driving down stairs;</li>
<li>Easily programmable tasks and IFTTT capabilities to connect within modern smart homes</li>
<li>Hours of battery life, and when it’s time to refuel, he simply returns himself to his charging dock for a quick charging nap.</li>
</ul>
<p>“While insanely cute on the outside, Kuri contains serious technologies on the inside that represent the latest developments in smartphones, gaming, and robotics,” said Kaijen Hsiao, CTO and co-founder of Mayfield Robotics. “We hope Kuri introduces people &#8212; especially kids &#8212; to the power of technology and can inspire a new world of possibilities for their future.”</p>
<p>“I’m excited to finally share the work we’ve done,” said Mike Beebe, Mayfield Robotics’ CEO and co-founder. “We have an incredible team that’s focused on a single dream: home robots done right.”</p>
<p>Kuri is 20” tall, weighs about 14 lbs, and includes an app for iOS and Android for setup and controlcapabilities. Mayfield Robotics plans to ship the first Kuri robots for Holiday 2017.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">###</p>
<p><strong>About Mayfield Robotics</strong></p>
<p>Mayfield Robotics is the maker of Kuri, a new kind of intelligent home robot. Born out of the Bosch Startup Platform, the company is a wholly owned subsidiary of Robert Bosch North America Corporation. Founded in 2015 by Sarah Osentoski, Kaijen Hsiao and Mike Beebe, the company is based out of Redwood City, California. For more information, visit www.mayfieldrobotics.com, and to pre-order Kuri, visit www.heykuri.com.<br />
Kuri makes life at home a little more interesting, fun and inspiring. He brings technology to life; he can understand context and surroundings, recognize specific people, provide companionship and more. Kuri is built to connect – with you, with others, and with your home.</p>
<p>The technology and computing power inside of Kuri is also remarkably powerful – from custom lasers and sensors, to advanced electric motors, a built-in camera, microphones, dual speakers, Wifi and Bluetooth connectivity, and more. If you want to really geek out, you can explore Kuri’s advanced internal hardware here.</p>
<p>So, what does this all mean for you? It’s what enables Kuri to check in on the house or pets while you’re away, read an audiobook to your kids at bedtime, follow you around and play music while you’re cleaning, or simply greet you at the door when you get home each night.</p>
<p>If you’re in the U.S., you can pre-order your own Kuri today. Visit heykuri.com, and reserve one with a $100 deposit. We’re planning to ship the first Kuri robots for the 2017 holiday season.</p>
<p>For more details on Kuri’s capabilities and features, check out our press release. And don’t forget to visit our blog from time to time, where we’ll be keeping you updated on Kuri’s latest developments.</p>
<p>We’re excited for you to join us on our journey to make home robots a reality. We believe we’re really doing home robots right, and hopefully we’ll enhance the lives of people everywhere along the way. Beep bloop!</p>
<p>Thanks for reading and stay tuned,</p>
<p>Mike, Sarah, Kaijen, and the team here at Mayfield Robotics</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-launches-at-ces-2017/">Kuri Launches at CES 2017</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-launches-at-ces-2017/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>18</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
