<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments on: What Is a Home Robot?</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/what-is-a-home-robot/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/blog/what-is-a-home-robot/</link>
	<description>Meet Kuri, the adorable home robot.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 23:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>By: Jennifer</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-a-home-robot/#comment-207</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 17:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=665#comment-207</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Hi Bob - Great observation. We actually have another blog post discussing Kuri&#039;s &quot;cuteness&quot; here on Kuri&#039;s home awareness capabilities that I definitely recommend checking out: https://blog.heykuri.com/cute-guard-dog/

To answer your second question, we chose not to have Kuri speak for a number of reasons. First, we wanted to create a home robot that brought joy to your day-to-day. Part of that meant reducing &quot;friction&quot; moments like Kuri not responding to a conversation in the way a human would. We&#039;ve all been there when a voice AI didn&#039;t hear us correctly, and that can be really frustrating for households. Given that Kuri was designed for households of all ages, we wanted a 4-year-old and a 90-year-old to have the same, seamless experience communicating with Kuri that&#039;d bring smiles to their faces. That&#039;s why Kuri &quot;speaks&quot; through audible &#039;beeps&#039; and &#039;boops&#039; and light displays - similar to R2-D2 from Star Wars. That way, you can give Kuri commands and have an adorable way to ensure it was acknowledged. Plus, you can play music, podcasts, and audiobooks using Kuri&#039;s speakers in any language you prefer - so she does speak English (or any other language) in that sense. ;)]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi Bob &#8211; Great observation. We actually have another blog post discussing Kuri&#8217;s &#8220;cuteness&#8221; here on Kuri&#8217;s home awareness capabilities that I definitely recommend checking out: <a href="https://blog.heykuri.com/cute-guard-dog/" rel="nofollow">https://blog.heykuri.com/cute-guard-dog/</a></p>
<p>To answer your second question, we chose not to have Kuri speak for a number of reasons. First, we wanted to create a home robot that brought joy to your day-to-day. Part of that meant reducing &#8220;friction&#8221; moments like Kuri not responding to a conversation in the way a human would. We&#8217;ve all been there when a voice AI didn&#8217;t hear us correctly, and that can be really frustrating for households. Given that Kuri was designed for households of all ages, we wanted a 4-year-old and a 90-year-old to have the same, seamless experience communicating with Kuri that&#8217;d bring smiles to their faces. That&#8217;s why Kuri &#8220;speaks&#8221; through audible &#8216;beeps&#8217; and &#8216;boops&#8217; and light displays &#8211; similar to R2-D2 from Star Wars. That way, you can give Kuri commands and have an adorable way to ensure it was acknowledged. Plus, you can play music, podcasts, and audiobooks using Kuri&#8217;s speakers in any language you prefer &#8211; so she does speak English (or any other language) in that sense. 😉</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: Bob Landstrom</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-a-home-robot/#comment-206</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bob Landstrom]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=665#comment-206</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Is it possible that Kuri is &quot;too cute?&quot;

People have pets.  Some people are cat people and some are dog people.  Some dog families adopt toy poodles and some adopt Labrador Retrievers.

We have both in our home, for example.  Little girls love the toy poodle.  Everyone else loves the Lab.

IMHO, the R2D2-like chirps amplify the cute affect.  Google Home, Echo, even Siri actually speak.  I&#039;m wondering why you chose not to have Kuri speak.

Anyway,... I love the concept.  This incarnation of the product is too cute for my taste, but best of luck to you!

Bob]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible that Kuri is &#8220;too cute?&#8221;</p>
<p>People have pets.  Some people are cat people and some are dog people.  Some dog families adopt toy poodles and some adopt Labrador Retrievers.</p>
<p>We have both in our home, for example.  Little girls love the toy poodle.  Everyone else loves the Lab.</p>
<p>IMHO, the R2D2-like chirps amplify the cute affect.  Google Home, Echo, even Siri actually speak.  I&#8217;m wondering why you chose not to have Kuri speak.</p>
<p>Anyway,&#8230; I love the concept.  This incarnation of the product is too cute for my taste, but best of luck to you!</p>
<p>Bob</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
