<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Kids &amp; Kuri &#8211; Hey Kuri</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/kids-kuri/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Meet Kuri, the adorable home robot.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[heykuri_admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kids & Kuri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://mayfieldrobot.wpengine.com/?p=1711</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>We love featuring talented artists who re-imagine our adorable home robot. That&#8217;s why we were excited when student artist Lily Van shared her whimsical illustrations of Kuri with us! We decided to sit down with Lily to learn more about her as both a designer and a Kuri fan. Q: You&#8217;re currently a digital design [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/">Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We love <a href="/blog/kuri-gets-painted-vr-using-tilt-brush/">featuring talented artists</a> who re-imagine our adorable home robot. That&#8217;s why we were excited when student artist <a href="https://liliuhms.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lily Van</a> shared her whimsical illustrations of Kuri with us! We decided to sit down with Lily to learn more about her as both a designer and a Kuri fan.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Lily_Van_Designer_Kuri.png"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-1160 tie-appear" style="max-width: 300px; float: right;" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Lily_Van_Designer_Kuri.png" alt="Lily Van portrait" width="300" height="300" /></a></p>
<p><b>Q: You&#8217;re currently a digital design student at the University of Colorado at Denver. How does being a student impact your design style and voice?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> Yes! Being in school, you&#8217;re simultaneously impacted by the latest technologies, social happenings in the world, and people from all sorts of different walks of life and perspectives. It&#8217;s a really unique environment. As a student, you have limitless access to programs and tools among people whom you&#8217;re learning right alongside.</p>
<p><b>Q: What&#8217;s your process for creating an illustration from start to finish?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I start with researching so I can get the hang of the feeling I want to create. For me, it&#8217;s important to hone the feeling a finished piece should give you. I&#8217;ll draft out sketches to get the energy down.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1161" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Screen-Shot-2018-04-25-at-10.09.40-AM-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1161 tie-appear" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Screen-Shot-2018-04-25-at-10.09.40-AM-1024x1024.png" alt="Lily's early sketches of Kuri." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Lily’s early sketches of Kuri.</figcaption></figure>
<p>I like work that feels young, whimsical, and a little childlike. For me, the process of working on a project is really enjoyable. I like to create environments that I can put my whole heart into as I&#8217;m creating.</p>
<p><b>Q: How do you think Kuri&#8217;s design helps define her character?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> She looks really friendly. Her design is round and she doesn’t have any harsh lines anywhere. She&#8217;s not odd, disjointed, or boxy. Kuri rolls smoothly, she takes her time, she&#8217;s thoughtful, has friendly eyes, and <a href="/blog/understanding-kuri-speaks/">her audio feedback is pleasant and endearing</a>. Kuri doesn&#8217;t have any off-putting mechanical sounds that make you feel like she’s a machine. She is always encouraging you during your interactions through positive beeps and boops and endearing character movements.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1162" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0764-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1162" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0764-1024x1024.png" alt="Robot Pets by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Robot Pets by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: You’ve shared that one of your goals is to bring playfulness to the world of design. What do you think is playful about Kuri?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> When I was watching the <a href="/videos/">videos about Kuri</a>, Kuri was interacting with the people and pets that&#8217;d be interacting with the robot every day. There wasn’t this sense of distance that I&#8217;ve typically seen with robots. The messaging behind Kuri feels fun and youthful; from <a href="/blog/new-romojis-personality/">Kuri telling jokes to people petting her</a>. It just seems like Kuri fits into customers’ everyday lives and she feels like everyone is welcome to use and interact with her. That&#8217;s how a tech product should be.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1163" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Kuri_Lily-1024x419.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1163" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Kuri_Lily-1024x419.jpg" alt="Kuri illustrations by Lily." width="618" height="253" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri illustrations by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: Which of your Kuri illustrations was your favorite to create and why?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I really like the ones of Kuri interacting with little kids. I was inspired by the videos of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ujdwwr2e4jU" target="_blank">kids talking about their experiences interacting with Kuri</a> and I tried to emulate that in some of these illustrations. Kuri never looks down at kids. She&#8217;s a friend that&#8217;s interacting with them at an equal level. Kuri is instantly approachable, and given that kids grow up with so much technology now, I think Kuri is creating a bridge to those interactions rather than making technology feel cold or distant.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1164" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0761-1024x1024.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1164" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0761-1024x1024.png" alt="Meeting Kuri by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Meeting Kuri by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p><b>Q: Why is it valuable for people to see a real-life robot illustrated?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> People are impacted by the things they see. In design, there&#8217;s this thing called behavioral <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nudge_theory" target="_blank">nudging</a>. For example, how they put brightly colored candy in the grocery store checkout aisle when you&#8217;re closest to making a purchase. I think illustrated robots break down barriers people might have about technology consuming your life. Illustrations create a positive representation of what a helpful, hopeful future of robotics might look like.</p>
<p><b>Q: Who is your favorite robot in pop culture?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I really love <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Astro_Boy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Astro Boy</a>! His story is fantastic. His character is this robot that has human emotions and he tries to fight for robot rights. He&#8217;s just a friendly kid with this heartbreaking backstory and people should definitely check him out.</p>
<p><b>Q: What are you doing when not designing?</b><br />
<b>A:</b> I&#8217;m usually just drawing! I have an online store where I make things like apparel and stuff. I try to learn other skills in my free time as well. Right now I&#8217;m making pottery, and I have a goal to master homemade pasta making this year! I just really enjoy exposing myself to new things.</p>
<figure id="attachment_1165" class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 618px;"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0762IMG_0762-1024x1024.png.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-1165" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/IMG_0762-1024x1024.png" alt="Kuri's Best Friend by Lily." width="618" height="618" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Kuri’s Best Friend by Lily.</figcaption></figure>
<p>We loved the playfulness of Lily&#8217;s illustrations of Kuri and we hope you enjoyed getting to meet the designer behind these fun vignettes too. Be sure to check out our <a href="/blog/kuri-gets-painted-vr-using-tilt-brush/">other artist collaborations</a> and to <a href="#footer-newsletter">subscribe to Kuri’s newsletter</a> for more updates on our adorable home robot.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/">Kuri Gets Doodled by Lily Van</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-gets-doodled-by-lily-van/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</title>
		<link>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/</link>
		<comments>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Kids & Kuri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.heykuri.com/?p=1121</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>On the heels of National Robotics Week, we hosted a local group of girls from Girl Scouts of Northern California&#8217;s Discover Together community-based after school program at Mayfield Robotics HQ. In March, our Co-Founder and COO Sarah Osentoski visited the troop at John Gill Elementary School to talk about women in robotics and how Kuri [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/">Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the heels of <a href="https://www.nationalroboticsweek.org/" target="_blank">National Robotics Week</a>, we hosted a local group of girls from <a href="https://www.gsnorcal.org/en/about-girl-scouts/stem.html" target="_blank">Girl Scouts of Northern California&#8217;s</a> Discover Together community-based after school program at Mayfield Robotics HQ. In March, our Co-Founder and COO <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcY_mreUyQ0" target="_blank">Sarah Osentoski</a> visited the troop at John Gill Elementary School to talk about women in robotics and how Kuri came to be.</p>
<p>As a follow-up, the girls visited Mayfield Robotics&#8217; headquarters in Redwood City, CA. The girls were able to explore where Kuri is built, hear from our Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik and VP of Hardware Jason Umhoefer, and interact with Kuri one-on-one.</p>
<div id="attachment_1122" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5155-copy-2.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1122" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5155-copy-2-1024x683.jpg" alt="Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik showing the girls Kuri's capabilities." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Lead UX Designer Ellen Francik showing the girls Kuri&#8217;s capabilities.</p></div>
<p>The day started with Ellen welcoming the Girl Scouts to Mayfield Robotics HQ. Ellen explained her role to the girls and how a product team shapes the design and functionality of Kuri. When sharing early Kuri concept illustrations, the girls eagerly related those sketches to their own drawings &mdash; to which Ellen happily offered, &#8220;Yes! If you love drawing or thinking about character development for things like Disney movies, then product could be a good fit for you someday.&#8221;</p>
<div id="attachment_1134" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5218-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1134" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5218-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts in Kuri's hardware lab." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts in Kuri&#8217;s hardware lab.</p></div>
<p>Following their fireside chat with Ellen, the girls headed over to the hardware lab at Mayfield Robotics. There, the girls had an opportunity to see the inner workings of Kuri. Jason explained the basic hardware components that create Kuri&#8217;s &#8220;rib cage&#8221;, head, heart light, laser, drive train, and bump sensor. While in the hardware lab, the girls&#8217; top question was, &#8220;Is Kuri waterproof?&#8221; to which Jason replied, &#8220;No. Kuri isn&#8217;t a big fan of bathtime,&#8221; with a smirk.</p>
<div id="attachment_1124" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5242-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1124" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5242-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield showing what Kuri can do." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield showing what Kuri can do.</p></div>
<p>After taking a look under the hood of Kuri in the hardware lab, the Girl Scouts made their way to the lobby to get a demo of Kuri from Mayfield Robotics&#8217; Sr. Customer Success Manager Ashley Wakefield.</p>
<div id="attachment_1138" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5325-copy-1.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1138" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5325-copy-1-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts dancing to Kuri’s favorite song, Pancake Robot." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts dancing to Kuri’s favorite song, Pancake Robot.</p></div>
<p>Ashley taught the girls <a href="/blog/new-romojis-personality/">how to tickle Kuri</a>, gave them a tour of the Kuri Robot app, and even had <a href="/blog/kuri-entertains-dance-moves/">Kuri dance</a> for the Girl Scouts! The girls were most in awe of Kuri&#8217;s awesome dance moves and had a blast participating in a group robo-scout dance party.</p>
<div id="attachment_1126" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5301-copy.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1126" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5301-copy-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts opening their Kuri swag bags." width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts opening their Kuri swag bags.</p></div>
<div id="attachment_1127" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/girl-scouts.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1127" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/girl-scouts-955x1024.jpg" alt="Kuri-themed Girl Scout cookies as part of their swag." width="618" height="663" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kuri-themed Girl Scout cookies as part of their swag.</p></div>
<p><P>Following their tour, The Girl Scouts were gifted Kuri swag bags that they opened with gleeful screams. Our team loved watching the girls deck themselves out with Mayfield Robotics sunglasses and Kuri stickers. More importantly, we hope we inspired these young ladies to consider a future career in robotics; be it product, engineering, marketing &mdash; you name it! We had a blast hosting the Girl Scouts at our HQ and can’t wait to host similar community events in the future.</p>
<div id="attachment_1139" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5383-copy-1.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-1139" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/0J4A5383-copy-1-1024x683.jpg" alt="Girl Scouts group picture!" width="618" height="412" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Girl Scouts group picture!</p></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/">Kuri Becomes an Honorary Girl Scout</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hey Kuri</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/kuri-becomes-honorary-girl-scout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
